
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "India has signed agreements with which country for Visa Facilitation and Leather Technology??",
    answer: "Ethiopia",
    options: [
      "USA",
      "Iran",
      "Ethiopia",
      "Japan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which state has passed an ordinance giving co-ownership rights to women in husband’s ancestral property?",
    answer: "Uttarakhand",
    options: [
      "Tamil Nadut",
      "Kerala",
      "Uttarakhand",
      "West Bengal"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Dr Syama Prasad Mookerjee Institute of Medical Sciences and Research’ has been set up by which institution?",
    answer: "IIT Kharagpur",
    options: [
      "IIT Madras",
      "IIT Delhi",
      "IIT Kharagpur",
      "IIT Kanpur"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which organisation has prepared a draft national migrant labour policy in India?",
    answer: "NITI Aayoge",
    options: [
      "NITI Aayoge",
      "Reserve Bank of India",
      "FICCI",
      " ASSOCHAM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "As per the new Information Technology Rules, digital platforms will have to provide required information within how many hours?",
    answer: "72 hours",
    options: [
      "12 hours",
      "24 hours",
      "48 hours",
      "72 hours"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which organisation is to commission India’s largest floating solar power plant at Telangana?",
    answer: "NHPC",
    options: [
      "NHPC",
      "NTPC",
      "REC",
      "BHEL"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which organisation has extended its support for India’s H2Ooooh! – Waterwise Program?",
    answer: "UNESCO",
    options: [
      "World Bank",
      "UNESCO",
      "UNICEF",
      "OECD"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which organisation has proposed to develop world class ‘Wayside Amenities’ at more than 600 locations in India?",
    answer: "NHAI",
    options: [
      " NTPC",
      "BHEL",
      "NHAI",
      "BRO"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Anandam: The Center for Happiness” has been inaugurated at which institution?",
    answer: "IIM Jammu",
    options: [
      "IIT Bombay",
      "IIT Madras",
      " IIM Jammu",
      "IIT Guwahati"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is “IH2A” that has been seen in the news recently?",
    answer: "India H2 Alliance",
    options: [
      " Covid 19 vaccine candidate",
      "Meteor",
      "New Plant species",
      "India H2 Alliance"
    ]
  },
];